in this lecture we'll use the shape
在这节课中，我们将使用
Builder tool to create the Helios logo I
用于创建Helios徽标的构建器工具
open the logo by going to file import
通过转到文件导入打开徽标
I right click on the canvas and choose
我在画布上单击鼠标右键并选择
document properties I click on the
文档属性，我点击
resize to content icon
调整到内容图标的大小
I turn snapping on
我打开了捕捉功能
I click on the rectangle tool and draw a
我单击矩形工具并绘制一个
rectangle over the logo which will snap
标志上方的矩形，它将捕捉
I set fill to none
我将Fill设置为None
now I will use the pen tool to draw a
现在，我将使用钢笔工具绘制一个
leaf when I hold my mouse at the top I
树叶当我把鼠标放在最上面的时候
see it snaps to the midpoint
看到它捕捉到中点
but the mouse doesn't snap to the center
但鼠标不会对齐中心
so I will go into the snapping options
因此，我将介绍快照选项
and check object midpoint
并检查对象中点
now I click on the object midpoint then
现在我点击对象的中点，然后
I click on the top midpoint and keep the
我点击顶部的中点并保持
mouse pressed down
按下鼠标
I drag and move the mouse to adjust the
我拖动并移动鼠标来调整
red line until the curve fits the leaf
红线，直到曲线适合树叶
then I let go of the mouse and press
然后我松开鼠标，按下
enter to stop drawing
按Enter停止绘图
I press the space bar to go to the
我按空格键进入
select tool at the bottom left I right
在左下角选择工具，我选择右下角
click and choose swap fill and stroke I
单击并选择交换填充和描边I
set the opacity to 50 I duplicate the
将不透明度设置为50我复制
path I click on the object flip
路径我点击对象翻转
horizontal icon I drag the copy until it
水平图标我拖动副本，直到它
snaps to the original path I hold shift
捕捉到我按住Shift键的原始路径
and click on the other path I go to path
然后单击我要转到的另一条路径
Union next I want to rotate the leaf and
联合下一步，我想旋转树叶和
make copies of them I click on the
复制它们。我点击
pathfx tab I open the menu and choose
路径选项卡我打开菜单并选择
rotate copies then I click on the Node
旋转副本，然后我单击节点
tool I drag the rotation origin point to
工具我将旋转原点拖动到
the midpoint where it will snap I set
它将捕捉的中点是我设置的
number of copies to 18 and press enter
将份数设置为18，然后按Enter键
to complete the effect I go to path
为了完成效果，我转到Path
object to path I set the opacity to 100
对象到路径我将不透明度设置为100
I duplicate the path Two Times by
我把这条路复制了两次
pressing Ctrl D twice now I click on the
按Ctrl D两次，现在我单击
shape Builder tool I drag over the outer
我将形状构建器工具拖到外部
leaves to select them
选择叶子来选择它们
as long as I keep the mouse pressed down
只要我按住鼠标不放
I will create a single path to show this
我将创建一条单一路径来显示这一点
I will let go of the mouse and select
我会松开鼠标并选择
the rest of the outer leaves I click on
其余的外层树叶我点击
finish as we see we now have two paths I
如我们所见，我们现在有两条路径i
will unite them by going to path Union
将通过走向联盟来团结他们
I will call the layer outer leaves I
我将这层称为外叶我
select the second path and click on the
选择第二个路径并单击
shape Builder tool to select the second
形状生成器工具用于选择第二个
row of leaves I click on them
一排叶子我点击它们
I click on finish and go to path Union I
我点击完成并前往路径Union I
call the path middle leaves I will click
呼叫中间叶子的路径，我会点击
on a green Swatch to make them visible I
在绿色的斯沃琪上让它们可见，
select the last path and click on the
选择最后一个路径并单击
shape Builder tool I select the third
形状生成器工具我选择第三个
row of leaves when I click on a wrong
当我点击错误时，一排叶子
Leaf I can remove it again using the
叶子我可以使用
delete tool I click on finish and go to
删除工具，我点击完成并转到
path Union I click on a yellow swatch
路径联盟我点击黄色样本
finally let's give the logo the correct
最后让我们给徽标正确的
colors I dragged the original logo to
我将原始徽标拖到的颜色
the left I will delete the rectangle
左边我会删除矩形
that I used for snapping I click on
我用来拍照我点击
outer leaves then I select the dropper
外面的叶子然后我选择滴水器
tool
工具
I click on an outer Leaf of the logo I
我点击徽标的外部叶子，
click on middle leaves and Sample the
单击中间的叶子并采样
color from the logo and I click on
颜色来自徽标，我点击
yellow leaves and assign the yellow
黄色叶子并指定黄色
we have now vectorized the logo using
我们现在已经使用将徽标进行了载体化
the shape Builder tool
形状生成器工具
foreign
外国